<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://qyfeng1021.github.io</id>
    <title>Gridea</title>
    <updated>2021-10-16T04:28:09.670Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://qyfeng1021.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://qyfeng1021.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>乱七八糟的仓库</subtitle>
    <logo>https://qyfeng1021.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://qyfeng1021.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2021, Gridea</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1. 职业摄影师们的建议]]></title>
        <id>https://qyfeng1021.github.io/post/1-zhi-ye-she-ying-shi-men-de-jian-yi/</id>
        <link href="https://qyfeng1021.github.io/post/1-zhi-ye-she-ying-shi-men-de-jian-yi/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-10-16T04:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>如果你的照片不够清晰，那么其他一切免谈</em></p>
<p>对于职业摄影师们而言，拍出成像清晰的照片极为重要，以至于他们为此专门创造了一个术语——“tack sharp”。数年前我第一次听到这个术语流传起来的时候，我自然而然地以为它来源于俗语——“像大头针一般锐利”。然而后来我在撰写本书时查阅了大量关于该术语的资料，结果令我感到尤为震惊。<br>
　　首先，它完全不是基于俗语“像大头针一样锐利”。实际上，它是取自于每个单词首字母的缩略词。TACK（Technically Accurate Cibachrome Kelvin)表示在技术上能准确地达到西巴克罗姆印相法效果的色温，SHARP(Shuttle Hyperfocal At Refracted Polarization) 代表在折射偏振下的快门超焦距。<br>
　　乍一听这些术语都相当专业，但如果当我告诉你，这些都只是我编出来的，你还会觉得它们很复杂吗？我打赌我在括号里补充的“光的色温”起到了作用，让你觉得这个说法更可信对吧？<br>
　　没关系，承认你被戏弄了不是什么大不了的事，就跟承认你以前拍的照片一点也不清晰一样。总之，别管那些术语了。重点在于要如何才能拍好一张照片，我想说的就是这些。</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[test]]></title>
        <id>https://qyfeng1021.github.io/post/test/</id>
        <link href="https://qyfeng1021.github.io/post/test/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-10-14T10:17:12.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In the face of current intricate and complex international situation, China will continually stick to the path of peaceful developments, adhere to foreign policy of building friendship and partnership with its neighboring countries, work with other countries to promote regional peace and prosperity. Since the beginning of this year, China has been working relentlessly to achieve steady growth while maintaining stability and economic progress through deepened reform and structural adjustment, shoring up market and public expectation about China's future development. China has the ability not only to achieve the expected social and economic development goals for this year, but also possible to realize constant economic development with good condition in the future, providing much more opportunities for South-East Asian countries like Thailand on development.<br>
China-Thailand cooperation has embarked on a fast lane of development. China-Thailand friendship has taken deep roots in the hearts of the two people and saturated into all aspects of people-to-people exchanges. I firmly believe that with closer exchanges between the two countries, the good neighborly friendship between China and Thailand will forge ahead incessantly like Chang Jiang River and Chao Phraya River, and our all-round mutual beneficial cooperation will enjoy a new brighter future.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>